Now is the time
这时候果然
for this newly wedded wife to sleep with you
还是由我这个刚进门没多久的老婆
to strengthen the bond between us.
睡在旁边培养感情才对
In that case, I should sleep the closest to him.
这样的话 妾身岂不是得睡在最靠近的位置
I share the deepest bond with him.
我和他的感情最深厚
I should be right next to him.
应该由我睡在最靠近的位置吧
I'd like to sleep in the middle.
我想睡在你们中间
Huh?
什么
I should just sleep in my own bedroom.
妾身还是回房自己睡
This is ridiculous.
有够蠢的
No. The more, the merrier.
不行啦 人越多越好
Distance will hinder the channelling of mana.
距离是魔力传递的障碍
Therefore, stay close to him.
总之你们最好待在他身边
Well...
那个…
It's just a little tearing of a wound.
我只是伤口稍微裂开而已
It's not as serious as you think.
不用看得这么严重吧
Satou, shut up!
佐藤你闭嘴
Yes, madam.
好
Sleeping with everyone here feels too weird!
话说大家一起睡也太奇怪了
We should take your feelings into consideration.
必须考虑佐藤的感受
Hey, didn't you just tell him to shut up?
喂 你刚刚不是叫佐藤闭嘴吗
You're getting on my nerves!
你好烦啊
Let us all calm down.
冷静点
In this situation,
这种情况
my instinct as a man should be cheering!
我的男性本能正在开心欢呼
But I can't follow my instinct and accept this madness.
但我不能顺从本能接受这件事
Everyone, listen to me.
各位 听我说
Whatever happens,
不管发生什么事
Hime always means the most to me.
对我来说 小姬都排名第一
Satou...
佐藤
I'm aware of that.
我知道这一点
I don't really care about my ranking in your heart.
我排第几名都无所谓
I will wait for as long as it takes.
无论多久我都愿意等
A brief moment of love is all that I ask.
我只要一时的爱就好
I'm also fine with any method.
因为我不在意任何形式
As long as you carry out your duty,
只要能让你达成使命
I can do anything.
要妾身做什么都可以
I will do anything for your sake.
为此 我愿意做任何事
What now?
怎么办
They weren't listening at all.
我说的话根本没意义
Satou.
佐藤
You don't have the slightest sympathy for the poor girls
原来你对我们这些 受到命运玩弄的可怜人
tortured by this ill fate.
一点同情心也没有呢
Therefore...
因此
we shall have our way with you!
现在就乖乖任我们摆布吧
Hold on, Granart.
等等 葛兰纳托
Ring King, my heart and soul are all yours.
戒王 我的身心都属于你
Hold on... When did you get naked?
怎么会 一下子就全裸了
Lord Satou, please teach me everything you know.
佐藤陛下 请你教我各种事吧
Not you too, Nephrites!
连涅芙丽缇丝都这样
What is going on here?
到底发生什么事
It's not bad this way.
这样子也不错吧
Not bad...
是不错啦…
Wait! That's not the point!
不对 重点不是这个
What is it? Why are you hesitating,
怎么了 你在犹豫什么
Ring King Satou?
戒王佐藤
Who's there?
是谁
Follow your power. Follow your desires.
顺从你的力量 顺从你的渴望
Just seize everything!
得到一切就行了
No. That still puts me in a tough situation here.
不 就算这么说还是很伤脑筋
I can't be with everyone at the same time.
我又不能同时陪所有人
Besides, I already have...
而且我已经有…
You seem troubled.
你很伤脑筋啊
You're the worst, Satou.
佐藤真差劲
Hime?
小姬
No! You got it all wrong!
不对 你误会了 小姬
This is just...
这是…
Hime!
小姬
You're the one I love the most!
我最喜欢的是你
Just a dream.
原来是梦
This can't go on forever.
这样子不行啊
Hime, let's go out today.
小姬 今天一起出门吧
Huh?
咦
What?
什么
TALES OF WEDDING RINGS
《婚戒物语》
Well... You know...
呃 那个啊
We've been staying in the palace ever since we came to the Kingdom of Water.
我们来到水之国后 就一直待在王宫里
I want to check out other places.
我想到处去看看
Nice idea.
听起来不错
It's going to be so much fun.
好像很好玩
Sorry.
不是的 抱歉
I only want to go with Hime.
我想和小姬两个人自己去
Are you just going to leave me behind?
要丢下我自己去吗
What is all the noise so early in the morning?
怎么了 一大早就这么吵
The Ring King needs rest before he recovers his power.
戒王恢复力量之前要暂时静养
As long as you stay out of trouble,
只要别惹事生非
you can go anywhere you want.
随便你们要去哪里玩都行
I got it.
好 我知道了
Leave this place to me.
这里就交给我
You two can have fun.
你们两个开心去玩吧
Right, Nephrites?
好吗 涅芙丽缇丝
Yes.
好
Are you sure?
这样好吗
You can count on me.
交给我吧
Thanks.
谢谢你
I thought Granart would be against it the most.
我还以为葛兰纳托 会是最反对的那一个
Whatever. This is great.
算了 这样真是太好了
I'm so excited.
好期待哦
The soap Saphir gave me smells great.
瑟菲珞给的沐浴露好香
I should use more of it.
多用一点吧
Hime, I love the scent of your body.
小姬 你身上的味道好香
I can't hold it anymore.
我把持不住了
Nah, just kidding.
开玩笑的啦
What?
什么
You're asking me for an allowance?
你想要零用钱
I'd like to go out with Hime.
我想和小姬出去玩
I don't have any money from this world.
可是我身上没有这个世界的钱
I see.
原来如此
So, how far will you take it?
那么你们打算走到哪一步呢
We are checking out the surrounding areas.
我们想在这附近逛逛
I mean your relationship with Hime.
我问的是你和克莉丝朵的关系
Don't ask me that all of a sudden.
不要突然问我这种事啦
Don't worry.
放心吧
I threw in a little extra money for you.
我有多放了一点钱
For your accommodation.
是住宿费
It's all right to spend the night outside.
你们今天不回来也没关系哦
I told you! That's not the plan!
都说了我没有这个打算
Sorry for the wait, Satou.
让你久等了 佐藤
This world is not the same as the world you came from.
这里跟你原本所在的世界日本不同
Don't let others' opinions bother you.
不用在意世人的眼光
Give it your best, young lad!
好好努力吧 年轻人
Where are we going?
你决定要去哪里了吗
I asked Saphir for a list of attractions.
我有叫瑟菲珞告诉我一些观光景点
Everything is planned.
都规划好了
Are you sure about this?
这样好吗
Should we be tailing them?
居然偷偷尾随他们
We are his wives, too.
我们也是他的妻子
We have the right to be treated as Krystal's equals.
享有与克莉丝朵同等待遇的权利
I see.
原来如此
Therefore, we must pay close attention to their relationship.
所以我们要关切他们的进展
If they ever get it done,
讲白一点 要是他们做了
we can use it as leverage against Satou.
就能用这点威胁佐藤
I get it now.
原来如此
I thought you dragged me out for something important.
把妾身拖出来 还以为有什么大事
So this is why we're here.
原来是这样啊
All the best.
你们自己加油
All right, let's follow them.
好 我们追上去吧
You must be the legendary Ring King.
你就是传闻中的戒王陛下吧
Welcome.
欢迎光临
Yes.
是的
To think you actually won the heart of our proud Princess Saphir.
你居然能追到 桀傲不逊的瑟菲珞公主
She may be intelligent,
那位公主虽然很聪明
but she's far from likeable.
却一点也不可爱吧
How rude. I'll remember you.
真无礼 我记住你了
You look surprisingly mediocre.
没想到你的外表还满普通的
I thought you'd be a lot more muscular.
我还以为身材会更健壮
Can I get your autograph?
请帮我签名
I'm off-duty at the moment.
现在是私人时间
This doesn't feel like a date.
感觉不太像在约会
Well, Satou seems to be having fun.
不过佐藤好像很开心
That's good enough.
这样也好
Satou isn't the Ring King today.
今天的佐藤并不是戒王
He is the normal boy I used to know.
只是我熟悉的那个普通男孩佐藤
Knowing that fills me with joy.
这让我很开心
When was the last time Satou actually
佐藤上次主动约我出门
asked me out?
是什么时候的事了呢
What is this?
这是什么啊
An authentic eel pie.
真正的鳗鱼派
It was me who asked him out
夏季庆典的时候
during the summer festival.
也是我主动邀他的
I thought I'd never see him again.
那时我以为再也见不到他了
Thank you for coming here, Satou.
谢谢你跟过来 佐藤
What... What's wrong?
怎…怎么了
You have a smudge on your face.
你的嘴边沾到了哦
Don't be so clumsy.
佐藤你真冒失
The mood is looking good.
他们的气氛还不错嘛
I envy them.
真令人羡慕
I also feel kind of lonely.
同时也觉得有点寂寞
Don't let this dishearten you.
不能因为这点小事就灰心
It's common knowledge in his world that one can only have one lover.
一个人只能和另一个人相爱 是他那边世界的常识
It's nothing more than a concept.
这种事只不过是一种想法
The world won't change because of it.
世界的常理不会改变
All we need to do is to change his mind.
我们只要让他改变想法就好
You sound imposing.
你真强势呢
Nothing can be done unless you show some determination.
如果连这点气势都没有怎么行
A park?
公园吗
A place where people go on dates.
这不是约会常去的地方吗
I never went on a date. I wouldn't know.
我没约会过 所以不懂
Me neither.
我也不懂
There is a fishing pond.
那边是钓鱼池
What is this place?
这是哪里呢
What is it?
我看看
When two people in love kiss each other here,
相爱的两人只要在这里接吻
they will be together forever.
就能永远在一起
Such is the legend of this fountain.
是这座喷泉的传闻
What? We should go in there...
什么 那我们也要…
It's just a rumour that started after I was born.
这只不过是妾身出生后 才出现的谣言罢了
This is so silly.
真是蠢毙了
She is looking at me.
她在看我
Is she waiting for me to make the first move?
这是在等我采取行动吗
Very well.
好
No! Doing that in public is
不 在公众场合做这种事
a little...
有点…
You have a point.
说得也是
Speaking of that,
这么说起来
I rarely get a chance to look at Hime's face so closely.
我好像很少有机会 这么近距离盯着小姬的脸看
Well, Satou,
我说佐藤
are you too embarrassed to kiss me?
你该不会是觉得主动吻我很害羞吧
Just as I thought.
果然是我想的那样
For me, you are...
对我来说 小姬是…
I can't stand this any more.
真是看不下去
I'm heading back.
妾身要回去了
Yeah.
也是
It seems a little mean to keep watching.
这么做对他们有点不好意思
You guys are no fun.
真无聊
I doubt they'd make any progress today.
不过这次应该没戏唱吧
Let's hope they do better in the future.
只能期待往后的进展了
What's so funny, Nephrites?
你笑什么 涅芙丽缇丝
I've never gone out and have fun with friends.
我从来没有像这样跟朋友出来玩过
I'm so happy right now.
觉得非常开心
Friends, huh?
朋友…啊
Don't you think the age gap is too big for us to be friends?
以朋友来说 我们的年纪差了一大截呢
Sorry... Sorry about that.
抱…抱歉
"MAGIC ICE CREAM" We'll have two, please.
(魔导冰淇淋) 我要两支冰淇淋
Right away.
马上来
Are you tourists?
你们是观光客吗
Or are you on honeymoon?
还是来蜜月旅行的
A special discount for the match made in heaven!
来 给登对的两位特别优待
This is huge.
超大份
This is the world where you came from.
我认为这是你出生的世界
I thought I should protect it.
所以必须守护它
But it's the same today.
不过 当然今天也是如此
The Ring Princesses and their nations,
但戒指公主和她们国家的人
Mr. Marse and Princess Saphira,
还有马尔斯先生和瑟菲菈小姐
are all normal folks
大家都是普通人
living normal lives.
过着普通的生活
This world and mine are not that different.
另一边的世界和这个世界没两样
I think that is great.
我觉得这一点很棒
Am I sounding like a hero?
这种想法会不会太像勇者了
Very much so.
很像哦
Even your expression looks like one.
连表情都变得很像
I never thought you'd become this way, Satou.
我真的没想过佐藤你会变成这样
It's getting dark.
快要天黑了
Let's head back after we finish this.
吃完这个就回去吧
I had a lot of fun today.
我今天玩得很开心
Thanks.
谢谢你
Oh...
哦…哦
I should confirm this.
确认一下哦
Can I consider this a date?
我可以把这当成是约会吧
That's what I think.
我就是这么想的
I see. It didn't look like a date?
这样啊 感觉不太像吗
Well... Don't get me wrong.
不…不是啦
We just never did this before.
因为这种事是第一次吧
I don't get why
我只是想不通
you suddenly asked me out.
你为什么突然邀我出来
We have feelings for each other,
难得我们两情相悦
but we've never done the things normal couples do.
却没做过什么情侣该做的事
That must feel great.
那个样子 真好
I want to be like them.
我也想变得像他们一样
It may sound weird,
这么说或许很奇怪
but I yearn for that.
但我也很向往这种事
I... I see.
这…这样啊
But you know,
不过啊 这种事
we shouldn't do it again in this world.
在这个世界 今天就当作最后一次吧
You can't always favour me alone.
佐藤你不能对我一个偏心啊
The others are your wives as well.
其他人也同样是你的妻子
I'm happy with the special treatment.
你给我特别待遇 我很高兴
But it's making things a lot harder for me.
但是这个样子也让我很难受
You carried out your duty as the Ring King flawlessly.
你完美尽到身为戒王的职责
But I...
而我却…
Don't be silly.
你在说什么啊
You're always the number one in my heart.
你是我心里的第一顺位
No! It has nothing to do with your place in my heart!
不对 跟顺位没关系
My heart belongs to you alone!
我的心里只有你
That is not right.
这样子是不行的
The Ring Princesses carried out their duty
戒指公主都是遵从使命
and made the decision to follow you.
下定决心跟你在一起的
You mustn't let their dedication be in vain.
你不能辜负她们的心意
You are worthy of being the Ring King.
你有成为戒王的资格
It's all the more reason to care about the others.
所以应该更为大家着想
But only you can have my heart.
我的心里真的只有你一个
If you still don't get it...
如果这么说你还不懂
I messed up!
搞砸了
I just did something really embarrassing!
我刚刚做了超羞耻的事
Let's... Let's head back.
回…回去吧
No. I don't want to go back.
不要 我不想回去
Only I can have your heart, right?
你的心里只有我吧
Hold on... Does it mean...
等一下 这该不会是…
Are we really going to do it now?
要做那种事的气氛吧
It's all right to spend the night outside.
你们今天不回来也没关系哦
Should I say yes?
我可以顺势答应吗
No! Now is the time
不 这种时候
to say this!
就应该顺势答应才对吧
Are you spending the night here or taking a break?
你们要住宿 还是休息呢
It's doable! The greatest first experience ever!
看来可行 最棒的初体验
Say yes, Satou!
快答应啊 佐藤
I can't believe I just said that...
我怎么会说那种话
Everyone is waiting for us. Let's head back.
大家都在等着 我们回去吧
Let's do it another time.
还是等下次吧
Why should I go too?
为什么连妾身都得跟去啊
You know why.
你应该明白吧
Without the mana from the Ring Princesses,
没有戒指公主的魔力
the Ring King can't battle the enemies.
戒王就无法战斗
But there are still the other three.
有她们三个还不够吗
Incredible! There's no limit to your stamina.
真可怕 简直就是精力无穷
Are you scared of leaving your homeland?
你害怕离开故乡吗
You never struck me as the cowardly type.
没想到你这么胆小呢
Look at Princess Nephrites, who was once a home dweller.
看看被称为家里蹲公主的 涅芙丽缇丝
Even she came with us.
人家都好好跟来了
Of course.
那还用说吗
I'm like an infant if you compare my age with hers.
跟她比起来 妾身的年纪就像小婴儿
That's right.
对了
Let Saphira go on my behalf.
干脆让瑟菲菈代替我跟你走吧
That seems to defeat the purpose.
这么做好像没什么意义
Just kidding.
我只是开个玩笑
Sorry. I never thought it'd turn this ugly.
抱歉 没想到事情会变成这样
I expected Marse to stay.
我还以为马尔斯会留在这里
No. It's all right, Sister.
不 没关系 皇姐
Prince Marse has found his purpose.
马尔斯殿下找到自己该做的事了
Besides, I love him because he is
再说我爱的
so honest and sincere.
就是他这种诚恳的一面
So...
那个…
Will you be all right without me?
妾身不在真的没关系吗
Don't worry.
别担心
While you are away,
皇姐不在的这段期间
Father and I will protect Maasa.
我会和父皇一起守护麻萨
Please stay safe, Sister.
倒是姐姐 你要小心安全
Use the power of your ring
然后请你用戒指的力量
to protect Prince Marse.
保护马尔斯殿下
Yes. You can count on me.
好 包在我身上
We are going to the Kingdom of Earth next.
接下来要去土之国
What is it like?
那是什么样的地方
The Kingdom of Earth, Idanokan.
土之国 伊达诺坎
It's located in the north, far away from Maasa.
在距离麻萨遥远的北方
It's a dwarven city standing on a tall mountain range.
位在高耸山脉上的矮人族都市
That's what I learned from the books.
书上是这么写的
Dwarves?
矮人
The kind with a beard and a ripped body?
就是留着胡子 身材健壮的
Well...
这个嘛…
Are we meeting a dwarven princess?
该不会是三头身的公主吧
Gramps, don't you know anything?
爷爷你不知道吗
The dwarves went extinct during the Ring King's battle
矮人族在戒王与深渊王的战争中
with the Abyss King.
就已经灭亡了
There is nothing but ruins of Idanokan left.
伊达诺坎现在只留下遗迹
Legend has it
据传说所述
that the people hated outsiders and were excellent craftsmen.
那里的人厌恶其他种族 拥有工匠的精神
They followed the Ring King
他们追随戒王
and fought the Abyss King bravely.
勇敢地与深渊王战斗
The already small population was significantly reduced.
本来就不多的人数又大幅减少
After the battle, they lived underground to hide from the world.
战争结束后 他们为了躲避人群 躲进地底下
Then, they simply faded from the world's eyes.
不知不觉就失去了踪迹
So, there isn't a Ring Princess,
也就是说 别说公主了
and much less rings.
连有没有戒指都不知道吗
But we are headed there now.
但我们还是朝那里前进了
You must know a thing or two,
你应该有什么头绪吧
Great Sage.
大贤者阁下
No idea.
没有
-No idea? -What?
-没有 -没有吗
We'll figure it out once we are there.
只能先到那里看看再说
If there's nothing we can do,
如果真的无计可施
we can come up with a different solution.
到时候再来想办法就好
We can see it from here.
已经能看到咯
The Great Mountain Range of Kaogamika.
那就是大山壁卡欧戈米卡
Idanokan is located
土之国伊达诺坎
on this towering mountain range.
就位在这高耸的山脉上
All right, we'll travel on foot from here on.
好了 从这里开始要用走的
Let's get moving, guys!
各位 快走吧
Seriously?
什么